<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Career Anchor</string>


    <string name="Q1">1 - I dream of being so good at what I do that my expert opinion is always
requested.
</string>

    <string name="Q2">2 – I feel more fulfilled in my work when I am able to integrate and manage the
work of others.
</string>

    <string name="Q3">3 - I dream of having a career that gives me the freedom to do the job my way and not
time programmed by me.</string>

    <string name="Q4">4 - Security and stability are more important to me than freedom and autonomy.</string>

    <string name="Q5">5 - I m always looking for ideas that will allow me to start my own business</string>

    <string name="Q6">6 – I will feel successful in my career if I feel that I have truly contributed to the well-being of society.
</string>

    <string name="Q7">7- I dream of a career in which I can solve problems or win in situations
extremely challenging.</string>

    <string name="Q8">8 - I d rather leave my job than be placed in a job that compromises my
ability to satisfy my personal and family interests.</string>

    <string name="Q9">9 – I will only feel successful in my career if I can develop my
technical and functional skills to the highest level of competence.
</string>

    <string name="Q10">10 - I dream of running a complex organization and making decisions that affect many
people.
</string>

    <string name="Q11">11 – I feel more fulfilled in my work when I have complete freedom to define
my own tasks, schedules and procedures.</string>

    <string name="Q12">12 - I d rather keep my current activity than accept another task that might put me at risk
my security at the company.</string>

    <string name="Q13">13 - Setting up my own business is more important to me than reaching a high
managerial position as an employee.</string>

    <string name="Q14">14 –I feel more fulfilled in my career when I can use my talents to
service of others.</string>

    <string name="Q15">15 – I feel fulfilled in my career only when I face and overcome challenges
extremely difficult.</string>

    <string name="Q16">16 - I dream of a career that allows me to integrate my personal needs,
family and work.
</string>

    <string name="Q17">17 – Becoming a technical manager in my area of expertise is more attractive to
me than becoming a general manager in some organization.
</string>

    <string name="Q18">18 - I will feel successful in my career only when I become a manager.
general in some organization.</string>

    <string name="Q19">19 -I will feel successful in my career only when I achieve full autonomy.
and freedom.
</string>

    <string name="Q20">20 - I m looking for jobs in organizations that give me a sense of security and stability..</string>

    <string name="Q21">21 – I feel fulfilled in my career when I am able to build something
that is entirely the result of my ideas and efforts.</string>

    <string name="Q22">22 - Use my skills to make the world a better place to live and
working is more important to me than achieving a high-level managerial position.
</string>

    <string name="Q23">23 – I feel more fulfilled in my career when I solve problems
apparently insoluble or I win what was apparently impossible to be won.</string>

    <string name="Q24">24 – I feel successful in life only when I am able to balance my
personal, family and career needs.</string>

    <string name="Q25">25 - I prefer to leave the company where I am accepting a job on a rotating basis that
move away from my area of expertise.</string>

    <string name="Q26">26 – Becoming a general manager is more attractive to me than becoming a director
technician in my area of expertise.</string>

    <string name="Q27">27 - For me, being able to do a job my way, free from rules and restrictions, is more
important than security.</string>

    <string name="Q28">28 – I feel more fulfilled in my work when I realize that I have complete security
financial and job stability.</string>

    <string name="Q29">29 – I feel successful in my work only when I can create or build
something that is entirely my own.</string>

    <string name="Q30">30 - I dream of having a career that makes a real contribution to humanity and to
society.</string>

    <string name="Q31">31 - I m looking for job opportunities that strongly challenge my abilities to
solve problems.
</string>

    <string name="Q32">32 - Balancing the demands of my personal and professional life is more important than
to achieve high managerial position.</string>

    <string name="Q33">33 – I feel fully fulfilled in my work when I am able to employ
my special skills and talents.</string>

    <string name="Q34">34 - I prefer to leave the company where I am accepting a position that takes me away from the path of
general board.
</string>

    <string name="Q35">35 - I prefer to leave the company where I am accepting a position that reduces my autonomy and
freedom.</string>

    <string name="Q36">36 - I dream of having a career that gives me a sense of security and stability.</string>

    <string name="Q37">37 - I dream of starting and setting up my own business.</string>

    <string name="Q38">38 – I prefer to leave the company where I am accepting a position that harms my
ability to be useful to others.</string>

    <string name="Q39">39 - Working on virtually unsolvable problems for me is more important than
Achieve a high-level managerial position.</string>

    <string name="Q40">40 -
I always looked for work opportunities that minimized interference with
personal and family matters.</string>

    <string name="hintquestoes">Between "1 to 6" how much do you identify \n with this statement?</string>

    <string name="txtintro">              CAREER ANCHORS\n\n
   In the 1970s, Edgar Schein, PhD in Social Psychology from the University
   of Harvard and professor emeritus at the Sloan School of Management, the school of
   businesses of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), in the United States,
   developed the theory of career anchors.\n
   Despite being old, the career anchor test theory is still valid for
   who seeks greater self-knowledge to direct their own lives
   professional.\n
   According to Schein, the anchors – eight in total – are pillars that guide the
   career decisions of professionals. The career anchors test, if aimed
   in making each professional discover what their anchors are:\n
   • A: Technical-functional competence;\n
   • B: General administrative competence;\n
   • C: Autonomy and independence;\n
   • D: Security and stability;\n
   • E: Entrepreneurial creativity;\n
   • F: Dedication to a cause;\n
   • G: Pure challenge;\n
   • H: Lifestyle\n
   They represent the unique combination of each in relation to the perception of
   career competence, motives and values. Knowing what your anchors are,
   it's easier to find the best company for you to work for, where your
   profile is aligned with the organizational culture.
</string>

    <string name="instrucaoquest">INSTRUCTIONS FOR STARTING THE CAREER ANCHOR TEST \n
For items 1 to 40 below, use the
following scale to rate how true each item is for
you :\n\n
1 - The statement is never true for me \n
2 to 3 - Occasionally true for me \n
4 to 5 - Often true for me \n
6 - It's always true for me \n\n
    Fill in one of the values mentioned above in each of the 40 questions below and then
        click on view results: </string>

   <string name="txtresultadoA">A - Technical-Functional Competence
Technically anchored people commit to a career in
Specialization. They are motivated when they are experts in a
a given subject, they are looking for challenging jobs, they want to test the
knowledge and skill they have in their area of expertise. They are
people who do not aim for high administrative positions (these usually
are more general) but specialist positions in a particular
area.</string>

    <string name="txtresultadoB">B - General Administrative Competence
Who has general administrative competence as a career anchor
seeks, throughout his professional life, to achieve the highest levels of
responsibility in the organization. They are people who aim at leadership and have
as a motivation to reach the top of the corporate hierarchy. For them, the
specialization is a trap: they understand the importance of knowing the
functional areas, but do not seek to delve technically, as
they want the general management role.</string>

    <string name="txtresultadoC">C - Autonomy and independence
People with this anchor will, over time, seek a career
that allows for greater independence, that allows them to impose their own
conditions. Autonomy is inherent in any human being, in levels
different, but those who have this anchor strongly feel the need to
be master of your own destiny, do things your way, and so will
organize your professional life around jobs that suit you.
provide more choice and decision-making power.</string>

    <string name="txtresultadoD">D - security and stability
Here fit people who need to feel safe in the environment of
work. They seek greater predictability of the future, they want to "know
where they step”. Are attracted to jobs in companies that offer this
stability, with good retirement plans and a good reputation. is this
stability, mainly financial, which will guide the career of these
professionals.</string>


    <string name="txtresultadoE">E - Entrepreneurial Creativity
This anchor includes professionals with the knack for creating new
businesses and organizations. They are not necessarily people with
artistic creativity, but with an entrepreneurial spirit, who want
establish or restructure their own businesses. Have motivation to,
from an early age, start ventures to earn money. It is worth mentioning
that the focus here is not the search for autonomy, but the creation of
Business.</string>

    <string name="txtresultadoF">F - Dedication To a Cause
People with this anchor are guided in their career by values that
want to print on your work. They turn to values and
they are dedicated to causes rather than to their talents and skills. They are
professionals who want, in some way, to contribute to a world
better through your work.</string>

    <string name="txtresultadoG">G - Pure Challenge
This anchor fits professionals who define success as
overcoming impossible obstacles or as the ability to solve
unsolvable problems. These are people who need to feel that they can
conquer anything. The search for challenges permeates the career of
most people, but for those who are anchored in pure challenge, that's what
guides your trajectory - all your professional decisions will always
be aiming to overcome increasing challenges.</string>

    <string name="txtresultadoH">H - Lifestyle
They often interpret this anchor as being that of people who do not
give priority to your career. But thats not what it is. The question is that
people anchored by the lifestyle seek to find a way to
integrate all your needs: individual, family and career.
They may be highly motivated by work, but understand that it must
integrate into your life as a whole. They are people who want, above
everything, flexibility. That's why they look more at the company's attitude than
for the work program itself. The difference to the anchor
autonomy is that they adapt well to the organizational environment, with
their rules and restrictions, but want to have more flexible work options.</string>

    <string name="btiniciateste">START TEST</string>

    <string name="btmostraresult">SHOW RESULT</string>
</resources>